pcsecurityshield.com 2013-04-03

# PCSecurityshield.com :: Privacy Policy

At **PCSecurityShield** we realize that privacy is important to all of our customers. We utilize your personal information only to provide you with free shipping related offers. This statement outlines how we care for your privacy.

**BY ACCESSING THIS SITE YOU ARE ACCEPTING THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY STATEMENT**. 

E-mail communications: When you register or order at **PCSecurityShield** we send you a courtesy confirmation. You also agree to receive the PCSecurityShield Shield Alert where we offer great offers on products from PCSecurityShield and its partners; security and antivirus news; and computer security tips. 

All communications will contain simple removal instructions.

PCSecurityShield reserves the right to share, barter or sell your information to our partners that may have offers that interest you. PCSecurityShield never shares your financial data. By agreeing to our privacy policy you agree to receive emails from our partners. All partners of PCSecurityShield maintain easily usable remove functions on every email that you receive and are all Can-Spam compliant. 

**Do you use cookies?  
**Yes. Cookies are a very important ingredient to our website. This is how we keep track your interests and provide you with a more enjoyable experience. You may disable cookies but you will only receive general offers not those specific to your interests. Certain web browsers may encounter difficulty checking out at PCSecurityShield. 

If you would like **PCSecurityShield** to keep ALL your information private and not share with any other of our partners, simply email us and we will delete and confirm such deletion with you. 

PCSecurityShield works with FetchBack to display Retargeted ads to our site prospects, on our behalf, across the Internet. They collect **Non-Personally Identifiable Information** about your visits to our Website, and your interaction with our products and services. The anonymous information is collected through the use of a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. No Personally Identifiable Information is collected during in this process. To read FetchBack’s Privacy Policy, click here <http://www.fetchback.com/privacy.html>. If you do not want FetchBack to collect this information, you may opt out of their service. Opting out will not in any way effect your use of our site. To Opt-Out, of FetchBack Retargeting, please click here <http://www.fetchback.com/optout.html>. Visit the Network Advertising Initiatives Opt- Out by clicking here <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>. 

**SHIPPING POLICY**   
**Canceled Orders**  
PCSecurityShield will accept order cancelations within 30 days of purchase. 

To cancel an order please contact us using our [Support Website](http://support.pcsecurityshield.com/contactUs/Default.aspx). 

**Shipping Methods**   
PCSecurityShield ships domestically via US Mail or FedEx and Airmail for **International** orders. Shipping costs are listed in the pull down menu for each item. 

**International Orders**   
PCSecurityShield only accepts orders to countries that are listed in the Pull Down menu. Due to the excessive costs of online fraud we have limited our international shipping. If you feel that you would still like to order from us but are not listed in the Country list, please email us. 

FedEx Shipping is **NOT** available for international locations. 

**Free Technical Support**  
PCSecurityShield provides free technical support for the life of the product you have purchased or the life of the product updates, whichever is less. Free Technical Support only includes issues associated with PCSecurityShield products and not the general operation of your computer. If after a PCSecurityShield product has been installed, operation of that product is interrupted due to actions of the user, PCSecurityShield will not be liable to provide free support to that user.

PCSecurityShield reserves the right to revoke free technical support on a case by case basis if it is deemed that the user continues to use PCSecurityShield support services do to actions of that customer. 

**Shipping Policy**   
Please feel free using our [Support Website](http://support.pcsecurityshield.com/contactUs/Default.aspx) if you would like overnight shipments. 

**Return Policy:**   
PCSecurityShield will accept returns for up to 30 days after day of receipt of good. Item must be in good shape and a restocking fee may be charged if there is damage. PC Security Shield will not reimburse for return shipping fees. 

After 30 days PCSecurityShield will issue a store credit only less fees.

**Lost Orders:**   
Order sent via first class mail can take 5-10 days to arrive. PCSecurityShield will not reship lost order for 14 days after the original order was placed. 

Please notify us within 20 days of order date if an order has not been received. After 20 days PCSecurityShield will consider the product received and the customer satisfied.
